

PROFILE

I offer 1 year of professional experience in development and 2 additional years of hands on experience on projects from a private university.

Currently I am working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK for J Sainsbury's.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

CONTACT

Phone:

+44 7448719858

Email:

atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian

HOBBIES & SPORTS

Badminton | Football | Chess

LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

ATANAS KAMBITOV

Software Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sainsbury's | Software Engineer | Coventry UK 03/12/2018 - Now (1 year)

Experienced with Microservice architecture and full-stack development including unit, integration and performance testing.

Hands on experience in .Net Core, React, SQL, relational and non-relational databases, Docker, Azure Cloud Services - DevOps, SignalR, Key vaults, AAD, Redis, Container Registry, Kubernetes, App Service, Azure Cosmos Db, Azure Service Bus, Event Hub, Stream analytics, PowerBl, MVC, MVVM.

Working in an agile way with scrum in a team of five people providing code quality, latency, stability and performance following solid principles.

SoftUni | Student | Sofia, Bulgaria 05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Hands on experience with backend API's, databases and frontend apps. Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines in a high pressure environment with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Agile Methodologies | Microservice Architecture | Azure | Solid Principles | MVC MVVM | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker | REST API | .NET Core | .Net Framework React.js | Redux | SQL | Angular | Typescript | JavaScript | Mongo DB | JQuery HTML5 & CSS3 | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js & Express.js

EDUCATION

South-West University "Neofit Rilski"

15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years) Bachelor degree in Informatics.

Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

DIPLOMAS & CERTIFICATES

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

Angular

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

React.is

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop